Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES V. Affiliates, 1930-80 (Part 1)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES V. AFFILIATES (PART 1)
  - Minnesota
    - Minneapolis
      - Plannned Parenthood, Publicity, Pamphlets, etc., 1960-1981 (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Minnesota, Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1969-1971 (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - Minnesota, Affiliation, PP of Minnesota, Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - PP, 1969-1971 (Box 160, Folder 14)
    - PP of Minnesota, Reports, Members, 1969-1971 (Box 160, Folder 15)
    - PP of Minnesota, Reports, General, 1969-1971 (Box 160, Folder 16)
    - Rochester, Affiliation, Olmstead County League, 1942-1956 (Box 160, Folder 17)
    - St. Paul
      - Affiliation, PP of Minnesota, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 160, Folder 18)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 160)
      - Affiliation, PP of Minnesota, Correspondence from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 160, Folder 19)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 160)
      - PP of Minnesota, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 160, Folder 20)
      - Merger: Minneapolis, Minnesota, St. Paul, 1971 (Box 160, Folder 21)
      - PP of Minnesota from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 160, Folder 22)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 160)
      - PP of Minnesota, Chapters, 1974 (Box 160, Folder 23)
      - PP of Minnesota, Field Visit Reports, 1976 (Box 160, Folder 24)
      - PP of Minnesota, Reports, General from 1972
        - 1971 (Box 160, Folder 25)
        - 1977 (Box 160)
      - PP of Minnesota, Reports, Members from 1972
        - 1972 (Box 160, Folder 26)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 160)
      - PP of Minnesota, Publicity, 1971-1977 (Box 160, Folder 27)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1951-1970 (Box 160, Folder 28)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence, 1957-1969 (Box 160, Folder 29)
      - Field Trips, 1952-1962 (Box 160, Folder 30)
      - PP, 1964-1971 (Box 160, Folder 31)
      - PP, Reports, Clinics, 1964-1965 (Box 160, Folder 32)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1964-1970 (Box 160, Folder 33)
      - PP, Publicity, 1964-1965 (Box 160, Folder 34)
    - Midwest Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1967-1969 (Box 160, Folder 35)
  - Mississippi
    - Anti-Poverty from 1965 1965-1974 (Box 160, Folder 36)
    - Contacts from 1964
      - 1964-1974 (Box 160, Folder 37)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 160)
    - Family Planning Association of Harrison County, 1972 (Box 160, Folder 38)
    - Hospitals, 1965 (Box 160, Folder 39)
    - Legal, 1962-1970 (Box 160, Folder 40)
    - Mississippi Council for Voluntary Family Planning & Southeast Region, PP Family Planning Workshops, 5/31/1972 (Box 160, Folder 41)
    - Council for Voluntary Family Planning, 1971-1973 (Box 160, Folder 42)
    - Programs & Projects, 1969-1971 (Box 160, Folder 43)
    - Public Health, 1963-1974 (Box 160, Folder 44)
    - Public Welfare, 1962-1970 (Box 160, Folder 45)
    - Southern Regional Council, Special Report on Mississippi, "Hungry Children," circa 1967 (Box 160, Folder 46)
    - Schools, General, 1965-1970 (Box 160, Folder 47)
    - University of Mississippi, 1963-1970 (Box 160, Folder 48)
    - Jackson
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1974 (Box 160, Folder 49)
      - Affiliation, PP Central Mississippi, Correspondence from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 160, Folder 50)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 160)
      - PP of Central Mississippi from 1973
        - 1972-1974 (Box 160, Folder 51)
        - 1975 (Box 160)
    - Gulfport, Biloxi
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, Documents, 1970 (Box 160, Folder 52)
      - Affiliation, PP of Harrison County, 1970-1972 (Box 160, Folder 53)
      - PP of Harrison County, 1970-1971 (Box 160, Folder 54)
      - Reports, Members, 1970-1971 (Box 160, Folder 55)
    - Southeast Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1964-1969 (Box 160, Folder 56)
    - Public Health & Welfare, Field Trips, 1952-1961 (Box 160, Folder 57)
  - Missouri
    - Anti-Poverty, 1965-1973 (Box 160, Folder 58)
    - Camdenton, 1971-1973 (Box 160, Folder 59)
    - Contacts from 1964
      - 1965-1973 (Box 160, Folder 60)
      - 1980 (Box 160)
    - Department Health, Education & Welfare, Regional Office, Kansas City from 1970 (Box 160)
      - 1970-1974 (Box 160, Folder 61)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 160)
    - Springfield, Family Planning in OACAC: 11 County Area Surrounding Springfield, 1971-1972 (Box 160, Folder 62)
    - Family Planning Council (Bootheel Area), 1970 (Box 160, Folder 63)
    - Family Planning Services, Hannibal, Missouri, 1972-1974 (Box 160, Folder 64)
    - Missouri Family Planning, Health Council, 1971-1974 (Box 160, Folder 65)
    - Hospitals, General, 1966-1972 (Box 160, Folder 66)
    - Legal from 1961
      - 1961-1974 (Box 160, Folder 67)
      - 1975 (Box 160)
    - Migrants, 1967 (Box 160, Folder 68)
    - Missouri State Medical Association, 1972 (Box 160, Folder 69)
    - Proposal for Statewide Family Planning Program, 1971 (Box 160, Folder 70)
    - Projects, 1970-1972 (Box 160, Folder 71)
    - Public Health, 1964-1972 (Box 160, Folder 72)
    - Public Health, Field Trips, 1961 (Box 160, Folder 73)
    - Public Welfare, 1966-1972 (Box 160, Folder 74)
    - Region VII, Family Planning Training (M. Fowler), 1979 (Box 160, Folder 75)
    - Resume of Activities in the State of Missouri, Related to Securing Federal Funds, 1971-2, 1972 (Box 160, Folder 76)
    - Rural Area Programs, 1971-1972 (Box 160, Folder 77)
    - St. Louis Metropolitan Area, Council for Voluntary Family Planning, 1972-1973 (Box 160, Folder 78)
    - United Fund, United Community Services, 1968-1969 (Box 160, Folder 79)
    - Schools, General, 1965-1973 (Box 160, Folder 80)
    - Washington University, 1964-1972 (Box 160, Folder 81)
    - Midwest Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1967-1969 (Box 160, Folder 82)
    - Charleston
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1966-1969 (Box 160, Folder 83)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 160, Folder 84)
    - MAPPA: (Missouri Association of PP Affiliates), 1975-1979 (Box 160, Folder 85)
    - Charleston
      - PP Association Mississippi County, 1966-1967 (Box 160, Folder 86)
      - Reports, Members, 1967 (Box 160, Folder 87)
    - Genesis of PP Chapters in Missouri: Springfield, Rolla, Kirksville, 1972 (Box 160, Folder 88)
    - Columbia
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1970
        - 1970-1973 (Box 160, Folder 89)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 160)
      - Affiliation, PP Central Missouri, Correspondence from 1970
        - 1970-1973 (Box 160, Folder 90)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 160)
      - PP of Central Missouri, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 160, Folder 91)
      - PP Association of Central Missouri from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 160, Folder 92)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 160)
      - Reports, Members from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 160, Folder 93)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 160)
      - Boone County (Inactive File), 1964-1965 (Box 160, Folder 94)
      - Field Trips, 1957-1958 (Box 160, Folder 95)
    - Cuba, PP of Crawford County from 1974 (An Affiliate of Rolla MO), 1974 (Box 160, Folder 96)
    - Kansas City
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1957
        - 1956-1972 (Box 161, Folder 1)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 161)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1959
        - 1959-1974 (Box 161, Folder 2)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 161)
      - PP Association Western Missouri/Kansas, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1980? (Box 161, Folder 3)
      - PP Western Missouri/Kansas from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 161, Folder 4)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 161)
      - Greater Kansas City PP, 1969-1971 (Box 161, Folder 5)
      - Greater Kansas City PP, 1967-1968 (Box 161, Folder 6)
      - Greater Kansas City PP, 1962-1966 (Box 161, Folder 7)
      - Family Planning Coordination between Kansas Health Department & PP Kansas City, 1969 (Box 161, Folder 8)
      - Field Trips, 1956-1962 (Box 161, Folder 9)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1961-1974 (Box 161, Folder 10)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 161, Folder 11)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 161)
      - PP, Publicity, 1961-1972 (Box 161, Folder 12)
      - "A Rationale for a Program in Sex Education," General Outline for Studies in Human Sexuality, Merle Zirkle, 1971 (Box 161, Folder 13)
    - Kirksville
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1974
        - 1973-1974 (Box 161, Folder 14)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 161)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1973
        - 1973-1974 (Box 161, Folder 15)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 161)
      - PP of Northeast Missouri from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 161, Folder 16)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 161)
      - PP of Northeast Missouri, Reports, Members, 1975-1976 (Box 161, Folder 17)
    - Pemiscot County
      - PP Project, 1957-1962 (Box 161, Folder 18)
      - Field Trips, 1956-1958 (Box 161, Folder 19)
    - Rolla
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 161, Folder 20)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 161)
      - PP Central Ozarks from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 161, Folder 21)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 161)
      - PP of the Central Ozarks, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1978 (Box 161, Folder 22)
      - PP of Central Ozarks from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 161, Folder 23)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 161)
      - Reports, Members, 1971-1974 (Box 161, Folder 24)
    - St. Clair, PP of Franklin County (An Affiliate of PP St. Louis), 1974 (Box 161, Folder 25)
    - St. Louis
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1949
        - 1953-1972 (Box 161, Folder 26)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 161)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1958
        - 1958-1972 (Box 161, Folder 27)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 161)
      - PP Association of St. Louis from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 161, Folder 28)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 161)
      - PP, 1964-1970 (Box 161, Folder 29)
      - Field Trips, 1956-1962 (Box 161, Folder 30)
      - PP, Reports, General from 1962
        - 1962-1974 (Box 161, Folder 31)
        - 1975 (Box 161)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 161, Folder 32)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 161)
    - Springfield, Affiliation, PP of Springfield, 1979-1980 (Box 161, Folder 33)
    - St. Louis
      - PP, Publicity, 1963-1976 (Box 161, Folder 34)
    - Springfield
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1973
        - 1973-1974 (Box 161, Folder 35)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 161)
      - Affiliation, PP Southwest Missouri, Correspondence from 1973
        - 1972-1974 (Box 161, Folder 36)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 161)
      - PP of Southwest Missouri, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1978 (Box 161, Folder 37)
      - PP Southwest Missouri from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 161, Folder 38)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 161)
      - Reports, Members, 1975 (Box 161, Folder 39)
    - Warrensburg, PP of Warrensburg, A Chapter of PP Western Missouri/Kansas
      - 1972-1973 (Box 161, Folder 40)
      - 1980 (Box 161)
  - Series V, Due to it's large size, the SERIES V container list is divided into two parts. Go to Part 2.